I can't believe they managed
to restrain you, Master Sasaki.
Pretty dumb, right?
I never thought Kyoshiro, my so-called
friend, would trick me like this.
Now...
What the hell caused this?
Well, Big Mom was fighting in the dome...
And her attack made it all the way out here?!
That's some insane strength.
Well, at least it got me free.
Anyway, I can't believe Kyoshiro
was one of Oden's retainers.
I don't give a rat's ass about Wano's history...
but he's going to regret double-crossing me!
Charge!
We shall put an end to this!
Exterminate the minks!
You cannot break our will!
We will take you-gara down!
Go ahead and do your worst.
This will finish you off!
Let us take care of the rest!
Wait.
Kin'emon.
Dog! Cat!
Let us handle this.
Indeed.
Such speed!
It's not just the Straw Hats...
Those are totally Udon prisoners.
Even Hyogoro's down there!
What happened at the prisoner
mining camp in Udon?
Did they threaten Babanuki?
This is Warden Babanuki in Udon.
Straw Hat Luffy, Captain Kid, and all
the troublemakers are locked in their cells.
So, I called to tell you all is well.
This doesn't add up.
I'm not going to blame you for all this.
After all, you've always been brainless.
You didn't have to say all that other crap!
We need to take care of this
situation immediately.
Now you sound like a leader!
Damn that Straw Hat!
Onigashima is in chaos...
Hawkins.
It wasn't your choice to join the Beast Pirates.
If you're planning to defect, now's the time...
Are you really asking me to betray them?
I'm no fool.
One percent.
What are you trying to predict?
The probability that a certain someone
survives until tomorrow.
Only one percent, huh...?
Poor bastard.
Come in, Soaring Six.
How annoying!
What do you want, King?!
Everyone...
As you know...
the situation has changed.
On the day of the annual Fire Festival,
we let the Red Scabbards samurai,
of all enemies, invade.
This is the biggest blunder
in Onigashima's history.
We must set aside our internal struggle,
even if Kaido encouraged it.
Our what?
This is regarding Young Master Yamato.
The one who returns
Young Master Yamato home...
earns the right to challenge
any of the Superstars for their position.
Although it pains me to say this,
we must put this on hold for the time being.
What?! Seriously?!
Of course.
Look around you, Big Sis.
Oh, Pay-Pay! Just who I was looking for!
Yamato got away by climbing the wall,
so you have to give me a piggyback ride...
No way.
You have to!
Shut up, you stupid kids.
– Who are you calling a kid?!
I'm not a kid anymore! Don't call me that!
Kaido is up on the rooftop.
The enemy is going to climb
to the top of the castle from the inside.
All of you will need to do
whatever you can to stop them.
Our troops number 30,000.
Their troops only number 5,000.
Still, don't underestimate them.
Good luck.
Hey, Drake!
There's an opportunity in all this mess.
Take a walk with me.
I can't handle it on my own.
Where are you going?
To kill the man I want to kill!
Let's pay Queen a visit.
Don't get me involved in your little spat.
Do you wanna weaken our forces?
He's useless anyway.
I'm not sure about this...
Straw Hats!
Allow us to clear the way to the castle!
Indeed! Conserve your strength
for the battle ahead!
Charge!
Get Straw Hat and his allies into the castle!
Don't allow them to recover!
They're just prisoners and yakuza!
How amazingly chaotic.
We must eliminate the large one, as well!
I can't believe such a human exists.
Do not hesitate! We must take him down!
Attack his feet!
Oh my, that was close.
Jinbe!
That's enough, you two.
Kaido!
Jack is one of my handpicked Superstars!
I won't just sit idly by as you
beat one of my best men to death.
Please... forgive me...
Viceroy Kaido...
You're no weakling, Jack.
It's just that these guys...
are too strong!
Thanks to these Sulongs,
we've taken serious losses...
But you did a good job
fending them off as well as you did.
Go get yourself patched up.
You've already done plenty.
What the hell is going on?!
You should be asking yourself that question!
You let Trafalgar Law escape
in the Flower Capital, didn't you?
We had a guard posted...
I figured it must have been you.
What's your objective?
I see...
The one you wanted to kill is...
...you, you piece of shit!
We should be ashamed
that we had a rat among our ranks.
What are you up to?
Are you working alone, or with a group?
Just who exactly are you?!
I guess this is it...
I can't talk myself out of this.
Unfortunately...
I won't talk even if you kill me!
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you...
My kind of torture
will break your spirit instead.
Bet you can't wait, huh, Drake?
Damn monster...
Straw Hat!
That thing is just like Oars.
Back then, it took all of us together
to bring down something that huge!
But things are different now!
Luffy!
Gear Fourth!
Boundman!
Oh, he did it again!
That form... He looks
just like a guardian deity!
All right.
Huh?!
What, not interested in the torture?
What a bummer...
Why don't I...
leave you all...
a parting gift?
Take cover!
Now what? How do I get away?
Is there no way back to the Marines?!
No!
No time to think about that now!
There's still one hope left!
Gum-Gum...
Get out of my way...
Juki!
X...
...Kong...
...Gun!
...Calibur!
That's...
...Drake of the Soaring Six!
Why did he attack the giant?!
There's still...
hope.
Crap!
Luffy is amazing!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I can't say why, but I've
just become an army of one!
Please!
Allow me to fight on your side!
Huh?!
What's with that guy?
He wants to fight with us?!
He's that perv who saw Nami and Robin taking
a bath the other day in the Flower Capital!
He just turned into some kind of dinosaur!
He must be one of those Soaring Six officers.
But... something's strange...
What in the world does he think he's doing?!
Hey, Drake!
Why did you attack one of the Numbers?!
Luffy is amazing!
He just makes you feel like...
like you're super close if you're friends,
but if you become his enemy,
he'll leave you in the dust.
That's the kind of guy he is!
What do you mean?
Luffy has this aura that draws people to him!
I know you!
You wanna take down Kaido too?!
I can't tell you why,
but we have the same goal!
Don't try to pull anything on us right now!
Luffy!
He's working for Kaido now,
just like Hawkins!
I was just removed from my position!
That's why you wanna side with us?!
How can we trust that two-timer?!
Stay away from Luffy, X Drake!
Even the world of pirates
is governed by a code of honor!
Sure, we can team up.
– No way!
Stay out of this, Captain!
You're such a dumbass!
Hurry to the castle, Luffy!
Okay!
I'll leave them to you!
Sanji! Let's get inside the castle!
Yeah!
The man in the straw hat...
I guess he's the boss
of all these pirates and samurai!
Let's go, Big Sis!
Keep those two away from Straw Hat!
– Yeah!
Move it, samurai!
You ultra-incompetent bumbling buffoons!
I fought those two in the castle!
That's...
the dinosaur from the Flower Capital!
But...
who's that cutie right beside him?!
You'll never see Kaido again!
Straw Hat!
Lethal... Green Star!
Skull Bombgrass!
Pay-Pay!
Wh-Who is that?!
I'm Nami!
What's your problem?!
Nothing I like more than exterminating lizards.
Now prepare yourself!
What the hell are you doing?!
Lizards?!
Prepare to be sprayed with lizard killer!
Don't hide!
How dare you shoot me!
Just who the hell did that?!
Oh, Pay-Pay!
It was that detestable tramp!
That's right!
I am the Great Lizard Buster, Nami!
Remember my name!
Knock it off already!
It wasn't me, but whatever!
The battle is already on!
Now...
Bring it on!
What?!
Your words don't match your actions!
Look who's talking!
I won't let you get away!
How could you hurt Pay-Pay?!
Look...
...how fast...
– ...we can run away!
– Hold it!
– Stop!
I'm counting on you, Usopp!
Protect my Nami!
Come on, Luffy! Let's meet up
with Kin'emon's group!
Yeah!
Hey, Sanji!
Cover your ears!
O-Okay!
Let's drop a battle beat!
Slash!
Looks like you wised up, Straw Hat!
But...
it's gonna be tough to fight if you can't hear!
Check it out!
Jaki!
Goki!
Juki!
It's too painful to see you guys like this!
Th-The ten of you...
have leveled countless towns together!
That's why...
it's just not fair to get
your asses kicked while drunk...
at such a delightful banquet!
Right?!
Don't you think so... Haccha?!
Are you sobered up now?!
There are ten of them?!
I'm gonna need more cola!
There's always strength in numbers!
Time to teach these lousy fools...
what happens when
an ancient giant loses their cool!
What?! Is he their tamer or something?
That jerk!
Forget about it!
We gotta go!
Fine!
Let's go!
Yeah!
It's just about showtime!
No room for you guys on stage!
This is a solo performance!
Don't stop, Luffy!
Yeah, I got it!
Look how strong he is!
Don't tell me he's going
to use his ally as a weapon!
Oh no!
Franky! Run straight out of the dome!
If we let this monstrosity run amok
any longer, the samurai will be overwhelmed!
Sure thing!
I'm counting on you!
Yeah!
Does he think the General Franky
is some kind of action figure?!
You're not getting your grubby hands on me!
He's gonna regret...
treating it like a toy!
At the very least...
it's a much better outcome
for me if you guys win.
Is that convincing enough?!
I see.
You're pretty straightforward.
But...
you're still hiding your identity!
We can't fight with a guy like that!
I just got a good idea!
Let's call in a few more Numbers!
Hey, guys!
Sober up and get over here!
Knock that shit off!
Yo, yo! I heard about you, Drake!
Are you gonna leech off that
itty-bitty pirate crew now?!
Scratchmen Apoo!
I've always hated this guy!
I'll kick his ass, but I'm not
doing it for you guys!
What's this? Common ground?
I don't like him either.
Looks like... we've got an alliance!
What the heck?!
Drake!
Don't think you can get away, you traitor!
I mean, you gotta be a spy!
You've got another freak coming after you...
Did you think that crap
would be enough to take me down?
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, stay with me!
Ouch! Dammit!
You're okay!
It's a shallow wound!
Is this...?!
Don't tell me...
this bullet...
Now... scamper around,
exhaust your strength, then die!
I can't wait to see how many you can dodge!
The thought never crossed my mind.
Blast Breath!
Foxfire Style...
Flame-Rend!
You thought we would flee?
How amusing!
We are done running!
And done hiding!
Let us die as Lord Oden's samurai!
Firmly grasping your severed head!